&gt；&gt；Kyle：当我们讨论使用块作用域的主题时，以及
&gt;&gt; Kyle: While we're on the topic of using block scoping, and
当我们在考虑是否或者
while we're on the topic of considering whether or
不让在你的函数的顶层是合适的。
not lets at the top level of your functions are appropriate.
如果你有这种习惯，就像你们中的许多人一样，
If you're of the habit, as many of you are,
在您的函数的顶层使用let，而您仍然希望这样做。
of using lets at the top level of your function, and you still want to do that.
我也要提醒你，很多时候你只会去
I'm going to caution you also that there are lots of times where you're only going
将变量用于几行代码，并且
to use a variable for a few lines of code, and
你不应该仅仅把它扔到作用域的顶层。
you should not just throw it into the top level of the scope.
您应该做的是为它创建一个作用域。
What you should do is create a scope for it.
打开一个圆括号对并创建一个范围
Open up a curly brace pair and create a scope just for
这三行代码使用前缀和rest变量，以及
those three lines of code to use the prefixed and the rest variable, and
然后，不要让它们存在于函数的任何其他部分。
then don't let them exist for any other part of the function.
不要只说let和prefix，还有
Don't just say let, and prefix, and
在函数的顶部休息，在那里打开一个圆括号。
rest at the top of your function, open up a curly brace there.
事实上，我在任何地方都会这样做，甚至在if语句中也是如此。
As a matter of fact, I do that anywhere, even inside of an if statement.
如果我有一个变量只需要存在于
If I have a variable that only needs to exist for
几行，这样做的方法是为它制作一个块。
a couple of lines, the way to do that is to make a block for it.
顺便说一下，这不是我的新发明。
And that's not a new invention of mine, by the way.
我们这么做是为了
We've done that for
在所有其他曾经有过块作用域的编程语言中工作了30年。
30 years in every other programming language that's ever had block scoping.
我们打开卷曲的括号对，我们把它放到块上。
We open up curly brace pairs and we scope it to the block.
我想说的是让我们用JavaScript来做这件事，因为它
All I'm saying is let's do that in JavaScript because it
在其他语言中工作得很好，是吗？
worked really well in other languages, yes?
&gt；&gt；演讲者2：你是纯粹为了语义而提出这个论点，还是
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Are you making this argument purely for semantics, or
做那样的事情对性能有好处吗？
is there a performance benefit to doing something like that?.
&gt；&gt；Kyle：你不太可能看到或
&gt;&gt; Kyle: It is extremely unlikely that you would ever see or
能够观察到任何性能差异。
be able to observe any performance difference.
理论上有表现上的差异，
There are theoretical performance differences,
就像理论上脱线程垃圾收集器可以
like theoretically an offthread garbage collector could
从理论上讲，垃圾收集得稍微早一些。
theoretically garbage collect it slightly earlier.
或者从理论上讲，它会减少可用于闭包的内容。
Or theoretically it would reduce what was available to a closure.
有理论上的原因，但在实践中，
There are theoretic reasons, but in practice,
几乎可以肯定，您不会以这种方式看到性能差异。
you almost certainly would not see a performance difference this way.
&gt；&gt；kyle：我只是说这样可以更清晰地沟通。
&gt;&gt; Kyle: I'm simply saying that this communicates more clearly.
顺便说一句，我是故意把我的曲子放进去的，
And by the way, I intentionally did put my lets,
这不仅节省了幻灯片上的空间，还有帮助。
it's not just saving space on the slides, it helps.
但我故意这样做，如果我要打开一个街区，只是为了
But I intentionally do, if I'm gonna open up a block, just for
像这样的几个变量的存在，
the existence of a couple of variables like that,
我将把我的声明放在与左大括号完全相同的行上。
I'll put my declarations on the very same line as the opening curly brace.
为了让读者非常清楚，嘿，这两个是为这个块创建的，并且
To make it super clear to the reader, hey, these two are created for this block, and
他们只是为了街区的目的而存在。
they exist only for the purpose of the block.
与之相反，你必须去寻找是否或
As opposed to, you have to go looking for whether or
此作用域中没有变量。
not there are variables in this scope.
你得去想办法。
You have to go figure it out.
我想让它变得超级明显。
I want it to be super obvious.
&gt；&gt；Kyle：我强烈建议您考虑使用更多的显式
&gt;&gt; Kyle: I strongly recommend that you consider using more of these explicit
让块，
let blocks,
缩小使用变量的范围，尽可能多地使用实用的变量。
narrowing the scope where you are using your variables as much as is practical.